{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Backyard Workshop Builders","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/62494/":{"taskOID":62494,"originalTaskOID":62494,"setID":9068,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":4329,"questionDisplayText":"Building Material","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Of what material do you want your building made?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":7048,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Wood","answerDisplayText":"Wood","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":750,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Aluminum","answerDisplayText":"Aluminum","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6069,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Steel","answerDisplayText":"Steel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6715,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Vinyl siding","answerDisplayText":"Vinyl siding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5680,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Siding \u0026 roofing to match home","answerDisplayText":"Siding \u0026 roofing to match home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4332,"questionDisplayText":"Features","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What features do you want for your building?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3647,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Loft","answerDisplayText":"Loft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4750,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Plywood floor on joists","answerDisplayText":"Plywood floor on joists","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1580,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Concrete slab floor","answerDisplayText":"Concrete slab floor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2191,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Electricity","answerDisplayText":"Electricity","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4741,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Plumbing","answerDisplayText":"Plumbing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7009,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Windows","answerDisplayText":"Windows","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5378,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Roll-up doors","answerDisplayText":"Roll-up doors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2102,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Drywall","answerDisplayText":"Drywall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3304,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Insulation","answerDisplayText":"Insulation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4555,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Painted interior","answerDisplayText":"Painted interior","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2546,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Flooring or carpet","answerDisplayText":"Flooring or carpet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1844,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Deck or porch","answerDisplayText":"Deck or porch","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":781,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Animal stalls","answerDisplayText":"Animal stalls","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5029,"answerDisplaySequence":14,"answerText":"Ramps","answerDisplayText":"Ramps","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1219,"answerDisplaySequence":15,"answerText":"Cabinets","answerDisplayText":"Cabinets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1182,"answerDisplaySequence":16,"answerText":"Built-in shelving","answerDisplayText":"Built-in shelving","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":17,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4331,"questionDisplayText":"Level of Customization","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What level of customization do you need?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4873,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Predesigned building package","answerDisplayText":"Predesigned building package","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1757,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Custom designed building package","answerDisplayText":"Custom designed building package","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1753,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Custom building to be constructed onsite","answerDisplayText":"Custom building to be constructed onsite","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio_LEFT","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio_LEFT","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11153,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Less than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11154,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":4329,"questionDisplayText":"Building Material","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Of what material do you want your building made?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":7048,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Wood","answerDisplayText":"Wood","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":750,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Aluminum","answerDisplayText":"Aluminum","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6069,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Steel","answerDisplayText":"Steel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6715,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Vinyl siding","answerDisplayText":"Vinyl siding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5680,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Siding \u0026 roofing to match home","answerDisplayText":"Siding \u0026 roofing to match home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":7048,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Wood","answerDisplayText":"Wood","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":750,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Aluminum","answerDisplayText":"Aluminum","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6069,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Steel","answerDisplayText":"Steel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6715,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Vinyl siding","answerDisplayText":"Vinyl siding","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5680,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Siding \u0026 roofing to match home","answerDisplayText":"Siding \u0026 roofing to match home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4332,"questionDisplayText":"Features","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What features do you want for your building?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3647,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Loft","answerDisplayText":"Loft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4750,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Plywood floor on joists","answerDisplayText":"Plywood floor on joists","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1580,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Concrete slab floor","answerDisplayText":"Concrete slab floor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2191,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Electricity","answerDisplayText":"Electricity","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4741,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Plumbing","answerDisplayText":"Plumbing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7009,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Windows","answerDisplayText":"Windows","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5378,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Roll-up doors","answerDisplayText":"Roll-up doors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2102,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Drywall","answerDisplayText":"Drywall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3304,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Insulation","answerDisplayText":"Insulation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4555,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Painted interior","answerDisplayText":"Painted interior","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2546,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Flooring or carpet","answerDisplayText":"Flooring or carpet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1844,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Deck or porch","answerDisplayText":"Deck or porch","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":781,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Animal stalls","answerDisplayText":"Animal stalls","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5029,"answerDisplaySequence":14,"answerText":"Ramps","answerDisplayText":"Ramps","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1219,"answerDisplaySequence":15,"answerText":"Cabinets","answerDisplayText":"Cabinets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1182,"answerDisplaySequence":16,"answerText":"Built-in shelving","answerDisplayText":"Built-in shelving","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":17,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":3647,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Loft","answerDisplayText":"Loft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4750,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Plywood floor on joists","answerDisplayText":"Plywood floor on joists","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1580,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Concrete slab floor","answerDisplayText":"Concrete slab floor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2191,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Electricity","answerDisplayText":"Electricity","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4741,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Plumbing","answerDisplayText":"Plumbing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7009,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Windows","answerDisplayText":"Windows","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5378,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Roll-up doors","answerDisplayText":"Roll-up doors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2102,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Drywall","answerDisplayText":"Drywall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3304,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Insulation","answerDisplayText":"Insulation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4555,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Painted interior","answerDisplayText":"Painted interior","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2546,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Flooring or carpet","answerDisplayText":"Flooring or carpet","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1844,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Deck or porch","answerDisplayText":"Deck or porch","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":781,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Animal stalls","answerDisplayText":"Animal stalls","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5029,"answerDisplaySequence":14,"answerText":"Ramps","answerDisplayText":"Ramps","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1219,"answerDisplaySequence":15,"answerText":"Cabinets","answerDisplayText":"Cabinets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1182,"answerDisplaySequence":16,"answerText":"Built-in shelving","answerDisplayText":"Built-in shelving","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":17,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4331,"questionDisplayText":"Level of Customization","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What level of customization do you need?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4873,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Predesigned building package","answerDisplayText":"Predesigned building package","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1757,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Custom designed building package","answerDisplayText":"Custom designed building package","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1753,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Custom building to be constructed onsite","answerDisplayText":"Custom building to be constructed onsite","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":4873,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Predesigned building package","answerDisplayText":"Predesigned building package","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1757,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Custom designed building package","answerDisplayText":"Custom designed building package","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1753,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Custom building to be constructed onsite","answerDisplayText":"Custom building to be constructed onsite","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio_LEFT","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio_LEFT","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio_LEFT","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio_LEFT","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11153,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Less than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11154,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11153,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Less than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11154,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"__cache./api/resource/task/62494/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":62494,"taskName":"Workshop - Build","taskDescription":"Build a Workshop","xmTaskDescriptor":"Backyard Workshop Builders","matchable":false,"profileable":false,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":null,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"workshop, shop, work, shed","textMessagingName":"Build Wrkshop","rolloverLongDesc":"Either custom, a kit built onsite or a ready-made unit brought in by truck \u0026 installed on-site. This refers to modest sized units suitable for a suburban back yard. Note separate category for full-sized outbuildings like those found on a farm.","rolloverShortDesc":"Includes pre-fab, kit \u0026 custom built models.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Build a Backyard Workshop.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area.","htmlTitle":"Workshop Builders \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Add a Backyard Workshop Shed","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":37,"acceptGoal":4,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Workshop Shed Construction","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Workshop - Build","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Workshop Project","urlName":"Workshop-Build","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Backyard Workshop Builders in \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Workshop Shed Additions","searchKeywords":"workshop, shed, garage, work","emcCategoryOid":-12063,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":9068,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}